Finding Aid for Claude Thomas Stoner Photographs and Papers 1870s-1977
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Classified Photographs
  - Ann Arbor Railroad
    - Union station (Ann Arbor and DTI), Dundee, Mich. circa 1910, [AA130] (Box 1)
    - Excursion train crossing Huron River, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1910, [AA131] (Box 1)
    - Steam shovel working in cut, Engine 18 on work train circa 1890, [AA132] (Box 1)
    - Engine 15, Toledo, Ohio 1896, [AA133] (Box 1)
    - Engine 43 circa 1905, [AA134] (Box 1)
    - Station, Yuma, Mich., [AA135] (Box 1)
    - Old station and dispatchers office, Owosso, Mich.; Passenger train with Engine 202, [AA136] (Box 1)
    - Old station, Elsie, Mich, with passenger train and Engine 201 circa 1910, [AA137] (Box 1)
    - Old station, Elsie, Mich, with Grand Rapids Board of Trade Prosperity Special circa 1910, [AA138] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train wreck, Elsie, Mich., with Engine 108 1911, [AA139] (Box 1)
    - Freight house, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1933, [AA140] (Box 1)
    - Timetable no. 47, First division 1914, [AA141] (Box 1)
    - Timetable no. 47, Second division 1914, [AA142] (Box 1)
    - Timetable no. 47, Third division 1914, [AA143] (Box 1)
    - Old Roundhouse, Owosso, Mich. circa 1905, [AA144] (Box 1)
    - Engine 45, Chilson, Mich. circa 1905, [AA145] (Box 1)
    - Engine 46 and freight train, near Chilson, Mich. circa 1905, [AA146] (Box 1)
    - Engine 41 and steam shovel, Chilson, Mich. circa 1905, [AA147] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train, Lakeland, Mich. circa 1910, [AA148] (Box 1)
    - Old Huron River Bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1903 with Michigan Central train, [AA149] (Box 1)
    - Wreck on Huron River Bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1904, [AA150-151] (Box 1)
    - Engine on passenger train after snowstorm, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1918, [AA152] (Box 1)
      See unclassified negatives for similar photo
    - Engine 13, early 1890s, [AA153] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5 and passenger train, Copemish, Mich., early 1890s, [AA154] (Box 1)
    - Engines 5 and 26, engine house and coal dock, Copemish(?), Mich., early 1890s, [AA155] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train after snowstorm, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1918, [AA156] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1520 Toledo, Ohio 1937, [AA157] (Box 1)
    - Snowplow 4501 Frankfort, Mich. circa 1930, [AA158] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 4, Frankfort, Mich. circa 1930, [AA159] (Box 1)
    - Football trains in Ferry Yard, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1930, [AA160] (Box 1)
    - Roundhouse, Durand, Mich. circa 1901, [AA161] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 and passenger train, Beulah, Mich. circa 1905, [AA162] (Box 1)
    - Carferries no. 5 and 6 in ice, [AA163] (Box 1)
    - Engine 46 on Maple River bridge, Bannister, Mich. circa 1908, [AA164] (Box 1)
    - Engine 126 circa 1920, [AA165] (Box 1)
    - Engine 127 circa 1930, [AA166] (Box 1)
    - Engine 130, Owosso, Mich., [AA167] (Box 1)
    - Engine 150 1909, [AA168] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2176, [AA169] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1612 with Train 51, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1949, [AA170] (Box 1)
    - Engine 150, [AA171] (Box 1)
    - Engine 159, [AA172] (Box 1)
    - Engine 200, [AA173] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1611 Owosso, Mich. 1937, [AA174] (Box 1)
    - Depot at Shepherd, Mich. circa 1912, [AA175] (Box 1)
    - Depot at Boon 1910, [AA176] (Box 1)
    - Diesel engine 1, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1962, [AA177-178] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 4, foundered at Frankfort, Mich., breakwater 1923, [AA179] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1614 Owosso, Mich. 1950, [AA180] (Box 1)
    - Wreck on Huron River bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1904, [AA181-182] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2171 (as USA 601), Fort Eustis, Va. 1955, [AA183] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1611 and Train 51, last trip, Howell, Mich. 1950, [AA184] (Box 1)
    - Engine 108, [AA185] (Box 1)
    - Clearing wreck, Marion, Mich. 1912, [AA186] (Box 1)
    - Wreck near Sherman, Mich. 1899, [AA187-188] (Box 1)
    - Engine 46 derailed, excursion wreck, Millersville, Mich. 1902, [AA189-197] (Box 1)
    - Engine 9 circa 1910, [AA198] (Box 1)
    - Engine 107 circa 1910, [AA199] (Box 1)
    - Engine 35, Frankfort, Mich. 1890s, [AA200] (Box 1)
    - Steam shovel buried at Bay Point, Mich. circa 1896, [AA201-202] (Box 1)
    - Station, Park Lake, Mich., [AA203] (Box 1)
    - Station with passenger train, Ashley, Mich. circa 1914, [AA204] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 and passenger train near Mt. Pleasant, Mich. circa 1900, [AA205] (Box 1)
    - Harbor at Frankfort, Michigan, with Carferry no. 2 in slip circa 1895, [AA206] (Box 1)
    - Loading Carferry no. 3 (?), Frankfort, Mich. circa 1905, [AA207] (Box 1)
    - Huron River bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1885, [AA208] (Box 1)
    - Huron River bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1887, [AA209] (Box 1)
    - Huron River bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1893, [AA210] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of DTI Engine 112, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1908, [AA211] (Box 1)
    - Station, Forest Hill, Mich. circa 1910, [AA212] (Box 1)
    - Station, Thompsonville, Mich., Engine 203 and passenger train circa 1910, [AA213] (Box 1)
    - Motor car 1, Thompsonville, Mich., with private car 1911, [AA214] (Box 1)
    - Engine 51, [AA215] (Box 1)
    - Motor car 5, Oak Grove, Mich. 1911, [AA216] (Box 1)
    - Steamer Northland entering harbor, Frankfort, Mich., early 1900s, [AA217] (Box 1)
    - Last run of Train 51 leaving Ann Arbor, Mich. 1950, [AA218] (Box 1)
    - Station, Beulah, Mich., [AA219] (Box 1)
    - Carferry Wabash, Manistique, Mich. 1938, [AA220] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train on Huron River bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich., middle 1880s, [AA221] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train on Huron River bridge, Ann Arbor, Mich., Engine 11 circa 1903, [AA222] (Box 1)
    - Motor car 1, Lakeland, Mich. 1911, [AA223] (Box 1)
    - TF1 with Engines 51 and 51A, Urania, Mich. 1951, [AA224] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 4 sunk inside breakwater, Frankfort, Mich. 1923, [AA225] (Box 1)
    - Engine 18, [AA226] (Box 1)
      (no print)
    - Motor car and old depot, Elsie, Mich. circa 1912, [AA227] (Box 1)
    - Motor car and old depot, Elsie, Mich. 1913, [AA228] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Bannister, Mich., [AA229] (Box 1)
    - Depot with train, Bannister, Mich., [AA230] (Box 1)
    - Depot with passenger train, Engine 201, Bannister, Mich., [AA231] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 4 sunk inside breakwater, Frankfort, Mich. 1923, [AA232] (Box 1)
    - Depot, Ashley, Mich. circa 1912, [AA233] (Box 1)
    - Depot, water tank, and freight house, Ann Arbor, Mich. circa 1900, [AA234] (Box 1)
    - Depot with Engine 6, Corunna, Mich. circa 1910, [AA235] (Box 1)
    - Engine 12 with passenger train circa 1890, [AA236] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 1, [AA237] (Box 1)
    - Carferries no. 1, 2, and 3, in ice, Frankfort, Mich. circa 1900, [AA238] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 5 unloading Carferry no. 4 after sinking, Frankfort, Mich. 1923, [AA239] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 3 and carferry Maitland no. 1, Frankfort, Mich. 1916, [AA240] (Box 1)
    - Carferry no. 7 after launching, Manitowoc, Wis. 1925, [AA241] (Box 1)
    - Scene at boatlanding, Frankfort, Mich. 1890s, [AA242] (Box 1)
    - Scene at boatlanding, Carferries no. 3, 4, 5, and 6, Frankfort, Mich. 1925, [AA243] (Box 1)
    - Wreck with Engine 185, Pomona, Mich. 1929, [AA244-257] (Box 1)
      (no prints)
    - Huron River bridge at low water, showing pilings of former bridges, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1971, [AA258-262] (Box 1)
    - Depot, coal dock, and motor car house, Howell, Mich. circa 1914, [AA263] (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor Street Railway
    (Code AASR)
    - Car on Packard Avenue circa 1910, [AASR1] (Box 1)
    - Car and crew at end of Packard Line, [AASR2] (Box 1)
    - View of South Main Street with car circa 1908, [AASR3] (Box 1)
    - View of South Main Street with car 751, [AASR4] (Box 1)
    - View of South Main Street with car 1893, [AASR5] (Box 1)
  - Ann Arbor & Ypsilanti Electric Railway
    (Code AAY)
    - Artist's sketch of train, [AAY1] (Box 1)
    - Train and military company, [AAY2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and train circa 1890-1895, [AAY3] (Box 1)
    - Train in front of Ypsilanti High School circa 1893, [AAY4] (Box 1)
    - Car 10, late 1890s, [AAY5] (Box 1)
  - Arcadia & Betsey River
    (Code ABR)
    - Engine 5, Henry, Mich. 1939, [ABR1] (Box 1)
    - Engines 4 and 5, Henry, Mich. 1939, [ABR2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4, [ABR3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4, Henry, Mich. 1939, [ABR4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5, Henry, Mich. 1939, [ABR5] (Box 1)
    - Narrow gauge log train on trestle, [ABR6-7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and train in mill yard circa 1895, [ABR8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and train at crossing, [ABR9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2 in mill yard, [ABR10] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 circa 1912, [ABR11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 and log train, [ABR12] (Box 1)
  - Atlantic & Gulf
    (Code AG)
    - Engine Sam Hill, Henry Ford Museum 1937, [AG1] (Box 1)
    - Engine Sam Hill, Greenfield Village 1958, [AG2] (Box 1)
  - Boston & Albany
    (Code BA)
    - Engine 1, [BA1] (Box 1)
  - Boyne City, Gaylord & Alpena
    (Code BC)
    - Engine 9, [BC1] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of Engine 10, [BC2-3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5, Boyne Falls, Mich., [BC4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5 and train, Boyne City, Mich., [BC5] (Box 1)
    - Snow plow scene 1922, [BC6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2 and cars on trestle over GR&I near Boyne Falls, [BC7] (Box 1)
    - Boyne City & Southeastern Engine 4, [BC8] (Box 1)
    - Boyne City & Southeastern Engine 7, [BC9] (Box 1)
    - Boyne City & Southeastern Engine 8, [BC10] (Box 1)
    - Boyne City Railroad Co. Engine 18, [BC11-12] (Box 1)
  - Burlington & Missouri River
    (Code BMR)
    - Engine 33, [BMR1] (Box 1)
  - Chicago, Burlington & Quincy
    (Code CBQ)
    - Engine 9, [CBQ1] (Box 1)
  - Columbus, Chicago & Indiana Central
    (Code CC)
    - Engine 369, Chicago 1871, [CC1] (Box 1)
  - Cleveland, Columbus, Cincinnati & Indianapolis
    (Code CCCI)
    - Engine 45, [CCCI1] (Box 1)
  - Calumet & Hecla
    (Code CH)
    - Engine Torch Lake 1966, [CH1] (Box 1)
  - Chicago Junction Railway
    (Code CJ)
    - Engine 21, Hammond, Ind. circa 1910, [CJ1] (Box 1)
  - Cadillac & Lake City
    (Code CLC)
    - Engine 11 and train, Lake City, Mich. 1964, [CLC1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11 and train, near Cadillac, Mich., [CLC2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11 and train, [CLC3] (Box 1)
    - Engine MX7, Lake City, Mich. 1966, [CLC4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, Lake City, Mich. 1967, [CLC5-6] (Box 1)
    - American Rolling Mills Engine B71, Lake City, Mich. 1967, [CLC7-8] (Box 1)
    - Ticket office, Lake City, Mich. 1967, [CLC9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, Lake City, Mich. 1969, [CLC10-11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 18, Lake City, Mich. 1968, [CLC12] (Box 1)
    - Wrecker, Lake City, Mich. 1969 gift from DTI, [CLC 13] (Box 1)
  - Canadian National
    (Code CNR)
    - Engine 5565 Petrolia, Ont. 1954, [CNR1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5565 with Michigan Railroad Club special train, Petrolia, Ont. 1954, [CNR2] (Box 1)
  - Chicago & North Western
    (Code CNW)
    - Engine Pioneer, [CNW1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 446 in roundhouse, Escanaba, Mich. 1951, [CNW2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1664 Escanaba, Mich. 1951, [CNW3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2810 Escanaba, Mich. 1951, [CNW4] (Box 1)
    - Diesel engine 4098C, Escanaba, Mich. 1951, [CNW5] (Box 1)
    - Engines 278 and 3, collision west of Hermansville, Mich. 1881, [CNW6] (Box 1)
    - Engine Pioneer, [CNW7] (Box 1)
  - Chesapeake & Ohio
    (Code CO)
    - Engine 471, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1951, [CO1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1245 Ann Arbor, Mich. 1951, [CO2] (Box 1)
    - Carferry City of Saginaw 31, Ludington, Mich. 1952, [CO3] (Box 1)
    - Carferries during strike, Ludington, Mich. 1952, [CO4] (Box 1)
    - High bridge near Brethren, Mich. 1950, [CO5] (Box 1)
    - Three unit diesel and empty hopper north of Columbus, Ohio 1955, [CO6] (Box 1)
    - Three unit diesel with train of refrigerator cars, north of Columbus, Ohio 1955, [CO7] (Box 1)
    - Diesel engines 97 and (?), football special, Ann Arbor, Mich. 1956, [CO8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1601 Greenfield Village, [CO9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 377, Lansing, Mich., centennial 1959, [CO10] (Box 1)
    - Engine 307 near Plymouth, Mich., [CO11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 377, Lansing, Mich., centennial 1959, [CO12] (Box 1)
    - Caboose 90382, Lansing, Mich., centennial 1959, [CO13] (Box 1)
    - Carferry Pere Marquette 21, Ludington, Mich. circa 1950, [CO14-15] (Box 1)
  - Central Pacific
    (Code CP)
    - Four engines, Roseburg, Ore. 1882, [CP1] (Box 1)
  - Cedar Point & Lake Erie
    (Code CPLE)
    - Engine 3 1965, [CPLE1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 with train 1965, [CPLE2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 1965, [CPLE3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 with train 1965, [CPLE4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 with train at station 1965, [CPLE5-CPLE6] (Box 1)
    - Engine Maud L at engine house 1965, [CPLE7] (Box 1)
    - Engine from Traverse City, Mich., park at engine house 1965, [CPLE8] (Box 1)
  - Canadian Pacific
    (Code CPR)
    - Engine 8470 and passenger train, Warren, Ont. 1955, [CPR1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3000, [CPR2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 5935, [CPR3] (Box 1)
  - Chicago & West Michigan
    (Code CWM)
    - Engine 32 circa 1890, [CWM1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 137 circa 1890, [CWM2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 22, Holland, Mich. 1888, [CWM3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 163, Muskegon, Mich. 1896, [CWM4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 116, Brookings, Mich. circa 1890, [CWM5] (Box 1)
    - Forney type engine circa 1880, [CWM6] (Box 1)
    - Chicago & Michigan Lake Shore Engine 8 circa 1880, [CWM7] (Box 1)
    - Inspection engine 130 and coach, [CWM8] (Box 1)
    - Grand Rapids, Newaygo & Lake Shore Engine 1, [CWM9] (Box 1)
    - Grand Rapids, Newaygo & Lake Shore Engine 5, [CWM10] (Box 1)
    - Grand Rapids, Kalkaska & Southeastern Construction train, Ricker's Mill, Mich. 1897, [CWM11] (Box 1)
    - Grand Rapids, Kalkaska & Southeastern Engine 1 and construction train, Ricker's Mill, Mich. 1897, [CWM12] (Box 1)
    - Grand Rapids, Kalkaska & Southeastern Engine 1, Ricker's Mill, Mich. 1897, [CWM13] (Box 1)
    - Engine 174 and log train circa 1898, [CWM14] (Box 1)
    - Rear end of log train, [CWM15] (Box 1)
    - Engine 33, [CWM16] (Box 1)
    - Engine 166 and freight train, [CWM17] (Box 1)
    - Engine 176 and log train, Stratford, Mich., late 1890s, [CWM18] (Box 1)
    - Engine, Woodville, Mich. 1880s, [CWM19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 139 and passenger train, Fremont, Mich. 1893, [CWM20] (Box 1)
    - Engine 175, [CWM21] (Box 1)
    - Engine 145, [CWM22] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2, [CWM23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 161, Muskegon, Mich. 1890, [CWM24] (Box 1)
  - Climax Locomotives
    (Code CX)
    - Engine 21, S. Rinard, Cranesville, W. Va., [CX1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 141, D.E. Johnson, N.C., wood rail, [CX2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 148, T.D. Collins, Tionesta Creek, Forest County, Pa., [CX3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 149, location unknown, [CX4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 181, with another engine, McDermott Stone Co., McDermott, Ohio, [CX5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 183, C.C. Masten, Svensen, Ore., wood track, [CX6-7] (Box 1)
    - Type A engine, Yellow Poplar Lumber Co., Barts Lick, Va., [CX8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 212, Wild Goose Railroad, Alaska, [CX9] (Box 1)
    - Type B engine, unloading from barge, Saldern Logging Co., Grays River, Wash., [CX10] (Box 1)
    - Wreck of log train with type B engine, Saldern Logging Co., Grays River, Wash., [CX11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 852, Central Pennsylvania Lumber Co., Tionesta Valley Railway, Sheffield, Pa., [CX12] (Box 1)
    - Type B engine, [CX13] (Box 1)
    - Engines no. 443 and 445, Corry, Pa., shops, [CX14] (Box 1)
    - Engine 260, Sierra Lumber Co., Red Bluff, Calif., [CX15] (Box 1)
    - Truck with brake beams, [CX16] (Box 1)
    - Truck without brake beams, [CX17] (Box 1)
  - Detroit & Charlevoix
    (Code DC)
    - Passenger train under bridge, Alba, Mich., [DC1] (Box 1)
  - Detroit, Jackson & Chicago
    (Code DJC)
    - Car barn, Ypsilanti, Mich., [DJC1] (Box 1)
    - Car barn and car, Ypsilanti, Mich., [DJC2] (Box 1)
    - Station at Grass Lake, Mich., [DJC3] (Box 1)
  - Detroit, Lansing & Northern
    (Code DLN)
    - Bridge, Grand Ledge, Mich. 1894, [DLN1] (Box 1)
    - Bridge, Grand Ledge, Mich. 1894 stereo, [DLN2] (Box 1)
    - Collision, Fowlerville, Mich. 1896, [DLN3-6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 26, Fowlerville, Mich. 1894, [DLN7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 20, Howell, Mich. circa 1893, [DLN8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 14, Portland, Mich. 1881, [DLN9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 41, [DLN10] (Box 1)
    - Engine and freight train, [DLN11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 13 and passenger train, Merrill, Mich. 1890s, [DLN12] (Box 1)
    - Engine 12, Lakeview, Mich. 1882, [DLN13] (Box 1)
    - Engine 44, late 1890s, [DLN14] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4 and passenger train, Howard City 1878, [DLN15] (Box 1)
    - Wreck, Fowlerville, Mich. 1896 engines 28 and 31, [DLN16] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and passenger train, Breckenridge, Mich. 1886, [DLN17] (Box 1)
    - Engine 39, Saginaw & Western Division, [DLN18] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3, moving depot, Grand Ledge, Mich. circa 1890, [DLN19] (Box 1)
  - Detroit & Mackinac
    (Code DM)
    - Engine 9 with mixed train, Mikado, Mich. 1907, [DM1] (Box 1)
    - Mixed train on Hillman Branch 1910, [DM2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 124, [DM3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 14, Rose City, Mich., [DM4] (Box 1)
    - Three engines in yard, Rose City, Mich. 1906, [DM5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 19 (?) with passenger train 1898, [DM6] (Box 1)
    - Detroit, Bay City & Alpena Engine 8, Lupton, Mich. circa 1893, [DM7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 115, East Tawas, Mich., [DM8] (Box 1)
    - Au Sable & Northwestern Engine 5 and passenger car circa 1910, [DM9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 150, [DM10] (Box 1)
    - Detroit, Bay City & Alpena Passenger train on Rifle River bridge near Omer, Mich. circa 1890, [DM11] (Box 1)
  - Detroit River Tunnel Co.
    (Code DRT)
    - Train 29 making first run through tunnel 1910, [DRT1] (Box 1)
    - Train 23 making first run through tunnel 1910, [DRT2] (Box 1)
    - Open cut and portal, Windsor, Ont. 1910, [DRT3] (Box 1)
    - W.C. Brown special 1910, [DRT4] (Box 1)
    - Motor 7510 Windsor, Ont. 1933, [DRT5] (Box 1)
    - Engines 163 and 162 with freight train, [DRT6] (Box 1)
  - Detroit (Mich.) Dept. of Street Railways
    (Code DSR)
    - Last trip on Gratiot line 1956, [DSR1-8] (Box 1)
  - Duluth, South Shore & Atlantic
    (Code DSSA)
    - Engine 717, wreck at L'Anse, Mich. 1952, [DSSA1-2] (Box 1)
    - Passenger train passing wreck of Engine 717, L'Anse, Mich. 1952, [DSSA3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 14 1911, [DSSA4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 74 1911, [DSSA5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 80 1911, [DSSA6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 90 1911, [DSSA7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 113 1911, [DSSA8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 208 1911, [DSSA9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 306 1911, [DSSA10] (Box 1)
    - Engine 401 1911, [DSSA11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 503 1911, [DSSA12] (Box 1)
    - Engine 602 1911, [DSSA13] (Box 1)
    - Engine 44 on bridge over power canal, Sault Ste. Marie, Mich. 1911, [DSSA14] (Box 1)
    - Engine 102 at Iron Bridge, Mich. 1911, [DSSA15] (Box 1)
    - Trestle at MP221, Perch River, Baraga County, Mich. 1911, [DSSA16] (Box 1)
    - Engine 102 on trestle, Bad River, Wis. 1911, [DSSA17] (Box 1)
    - Trestle, Bad River, Wis. 1911, [DSSA18] (Box 1)
    - Engine 102 with engine house and water tank, Houghton, Mich. 1911, [DSSA19] (Box 1)
    - Bridge, Agate Falls, Middle Branch Ontonagon River, Mich. 1911, [DSSA20] (Box 1)
    - Mackinac Transportation Co. Carferry, Ste. Marie 1911, [DSSA21] (Box 1)
    - Mackinac Transportation Co. Carferry, St. Ignace 1911, [DSSA22] (Box 1)
    - Observation and cafe car 1911, [DSSA23] (Box 1)
    - Water tank, Au Train, Mich. 1911, [DSSA24] (Box 1)
    - Four-wheel caboose 503 1911, [DSSA25] (Box 1)
    - Ore car 3892, [DSSA26] (Box 1)
    - Ore car 7520, [DSSA27] (Box 1)
    - Engine 500 and passenger train on bridge, Sault Ste. Marie, Mich., [DSSA28] (Box 1)
    - Budd RDC Shoreliner 500, [DSSA29] (Box 1)
    - Engine 552, [DSSA30] (Box 1)
    - Engines 14 and 19 on ore dock, Marquette, Mich., [DSSA31] (Box 1)
    - Engine 412 and ore train 1890s, [DSSA32] (Box 1)
    - Engines 206 and 406 with pusher, freight train, Quincy Hill, Mich. 1890s, [DSSA33] (Box 1)
    - Marquette, Houghton & Ontonagon Engine 36 1880s, [DSSA34] (Box 1)
    - Marquette, Houghton & Ontonagon Engine 40 1880s, [DSSA35] (Box 1)
    - Engine 2 being fished out of lake after going off end of ore dock, Marquette, Mich. 1893, [DSSA36] (Box 1)
    - Engine 4, Marquette, Mich. 1890s, [DSSA37] (Box 1)
    - Mackinac Transportation Co. Carferry Chief Wawatam, St. Ignace, Mich. 1972, [DSSA38] (Box 1)
  - Detroit, Toledo & Ironton
    (Code DTI)
    - Engine 311, [DTI1-2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 16, [DTI3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 7 1924, [DTI4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 22 1924, [DTI5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 16 1923, [DTI6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 45 1927, [DTI7] (Box 1)
    - Engine 60 1927, [DTI8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 72 1926, [DTI9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 75 1926, [DTI10] (Box 1)
  - Detroit & Toledo Shore Line
    (Code DTSL)
    - Engine 14, [DTSL1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 109, [DTSL2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8 circa 1911, [DTSL3] (Box 1)
  - East Jordan & Southern
    (Code EJS)
    - Engine 8, East Jordan, Mich., station, [EJS1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8, [EJS2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 in park, East Jordan, Mich. 1963, [EJS3-4] (Box 1)
    - Station, East Jordan, Mich., [EJS5] (Box 1)
    - Engine ML1 and combine no. 2, [EJS6] (Box 1)
    - Engine ML1, [EJS7-8] (Box 1)
    - Combine no. 2, [EJS9-11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6, [EJS12] (Box 1)
  - Escanaba & Lake Superior
    (Code ELS)
    - Engine 16, [ELS1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 8, [ELS2] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11, [ELS3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11, Wells, Mich. 1936, [ELS4] (Box 1)
  - Erie & Michigan Railway & Navigation
    (Code EM)
    - Engine 9, [EM1-2] (Box 1)
  - Erie Railroad
    (Code ERIE)
    - Engine 4020 builders photo, [ERIE1] (Box 1)
  - Empire & South Eastern
    (Code ESE)
    - Engine 3, [ESE1] (Box 1)
  - Experimental engines
    (Code EX)
    - Fontaine engine, built by Grant 1880, [EX1] (Box 1)
    - Raub's Central Power, built by Grant 1888, [EX2] (Box 1)
    - Soo Line Engine 6, Holman patent, [EX3] (Box 1)
  - Flint & Pere Marquette
    (Code FPM)
    - Engine 68 and cars at Stearns and Olson mill circa 1890, [FPM3] (Box 1)
    - Flatcar and load of logs circa 1890, [FPM4] (Box 1)
    - Engine 99, [FPM5] (Box 1)
    - Engine 10, [FPM6] (Box 1)
    - Engine 55, [FPM7] (Box 1)
    - Excavator no. 1, [FPM8] (Box 1)
    - Engine 16, [FPM9] (Box 1)
    - Engine 95, [FPM10] (Box 1)
    - Port Huron & North Western Passenger train, Port Huron, Mich. circa 1880, [FPM11] (Box 1)
    - Engine 52 and log train at Wright & Ketchum banking ground on Tittabawassee River, [FPM12] (Box 1)
    - Engine 55 and log train, [FPM13] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and passenger train 1870s, [FPM14] (Box 1)
    - Engine 9 and train, [FPM15] (Box 1)
    - Engine 11, [FPM16] (Box 1)
    - Pay car 43, [FPM17] (Box 1)
    - Port Huron & North Western Engine 10, [FPM18] (Box 1)
    - Port Huron & North Western Engine 12, [FPM19] (Box 1)
    - Engine 6 and train, Farwell, Mich. 1870s, [FPM20] (Box 1)
    - Engine 78 and log train, [FPM21] (Box 1)
    - Engine 87 after wreck, [FPM22] (Box 1)
    - Engine 3 and passenger train, Mount Pleasant, Mich. 1896, [FPM23] (Box 1)
    - Engine 40 and log train, [FPM24] (Box 1)
    - Yard, Palms, Mich. 1894 showing double gauge track, [FPM25] (Box 1)
    - Flint & Holly Engine H.H. Crapo circa 1865, [FPM26] (Box 1)
    - Engine 115 and log train near Farwell, Mich., [FPM27] (Box 1)
  - Frankfort & Southeastern
    (Code FSE)
    - Engine 1 and train 1889, [FSE1] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 1889, [FSE2; this is a detail of FSE3] (Box 1)
    - Engine 1 with flatcar and crew 1889, [FSE3] (Box 1)
    - Old Benzonia station (now Beulah, Mich.) 1890, [FSE4] (Box 1)
    - Crystal Lake just east of old station, Crystal City, Mich. 1889-1890, [FSE5a-5c] (Box 1)
    - First train at Crystal City (Beulah, Mich.) 1889, [FSE6] (Box 1)